sendmybag.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy at Send My Bag

#### 1\. GENERAL

The following privacy policy applies to the website services provided by Sendmybag (NI) Limited (Sendmybag) at www.sendmybag.com

Sendmybag is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and that it complies with its obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998, which regulates the processing of information relating to you and grants you various rights in relation to your personal data.

By accessing the Sendmybag website, you are agreeing to the following policy from the date of first registration or usage. We may change these terms and conditions from time to time and will post revisions on our websites. We advise that you review these terms and conditions regularly.

#### 2\. REGISTRATION DATA

When you first access a Sendmybag website, we will collect personal information from you. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem to our helpdesk and may keep a record of any correspondence. All telephone calls to and from Sendmybag are recorded for training and monitoring purposes.

#### 3\. AGGREGATED DATA

We may anonymise your data and aggregate it with data from other users to understand how people are using our website and to evaluate our services. We reserve the right to disclose anonymised aggregated user data to approved third parties.

#### 4\. USER-GENERATED DATA

Should you contribute user-generated content to our website environment, including any contribution to a forum or chat, or supply session feedback, some of your personal data (such as your name and email address) may be displayed on the website. When submitting user-generated content (such as a forum posting or chat), you acknowledge and agree that Sendmybag may access, preserve, and disclose your account information and any content posted by you in order to: (a) comply with any legal process; (b) enforce the terms and conditions of use; (c) respond to claims that any content posted violates the rights of third parties; (d) respond to your requests for customer service; (e) contact you to undertake further evaluation) or (f) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Sendmybag, other users of the website and the public.

#### 5\. COMMUNICATIONS AND BULLETINS

If you have completed our double opt in process, from time to time Sendmybag may email you with information about other services that may be of interest to you. If you should decide that you do not wish to receive such communications you may opt out of receipt of similar future emails by clicking the opt out link in the email or contacting us at info@sendmybag.com

#### 6\. MAKING CHANGES TO YOUR INFORMATION

Where your details become outdated you should update your details in the secure area of the Sendmybag website.

#### 7\. IP ADDRESSES

We may record your computer's IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration purposes and to enable us to gather information on website usage. These data enable us to track browsing patterns, and are not used to identify you as an individual.

#### 8\. SECURITY

Your personal information is stored and processed by Sendmybag in compliance with the Data Protection Act (1998). Your data is held securely on our databases which are only available to authorised Sendmybag personnel on a password protected basis and is not available to any other individual or party. Your information is protected by a firewall. We also use system and application logs to track all access. We review these logs periodically and investigate any anomalies or discrepancies.  
Although all reasonable efforts will be taken to ensure security of personal data, it is not possible for Sendmybag to guarantee 100% data security.

#### 9\. AUTHENTICATION

You are responsible for ensuring that your Sendmybag account password remains secure. You should not disclose your user name and password to other people. If you forget your password, please contact us at info@sendmybag.com 

#### 10\. EMAIL SECURITY

Any email correspondence between you and Sendmybag will not be encrypted. Emails received by Sendmybag will be stored securely within our corporate firewall.

#### 11\. USE OF COOKIES

A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Cookies allow us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements, to determine how frequently particular pages are visited and to determine the most popular areas of our web site. We use cookies so that we can give you a better experience when you return to our web site.

The Sendmybag website uses cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

#### 12\. LINKING TO EXTERNAL SITES

When using the Sendmybag website and materials, you will encounter links to external websites. Please be aware that once you click to one of these sites, you are subject to that site's privacy policy and Sendmybag can accept no responsibility for your privacy in relation to your use of external websites.

#### 13\. YOUR CONSENT

By submitting your information to Sendmybag, you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. You should review this policy regularly, to note any changes as to how we collect and use personal information.

Thank you for reviewing this information. If you have any questions about this policy, please contact info@sendmybag.com

#### 14\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

We may occasionally modify our Privacy Policy; when this happens, we will publish details on this web page. We will not however significantly change how we use information you have already given to us without your prior agreement.

#### 15\. YOUR RIGHTS TO ACCESS PERSONAL INFORMATION

You have the right to receive information about the personal data (as defined in the Data Protection Act 1998) we maintain on you upon written request and payment of a fee. If you are concerned that any of the information we hold on you is incorrect please contact us.
